NANCY A. NOLAN

6314 N. Kerby Ave., Portland, OR 97217 nancyanolan@gmail.com 541-279-3261

PROFILE

Experienced, highly organized, detail oriented professional puts an emphasis on quality work, prioritizing and clear communication while taking on a high degree of responsibility.

Creative in solutions, research and independently identifying and handling needs in day-to-day business. Learns and utilizes new applications easily and quickly.

EXPERIENCE

REAL ESTATE BROKER: JMA PROPERTIES, LLC, PORTLAND, OR 2012 - Current

Full service Real Estate Broker creating relationships with leads to gain clients; list and show homes; negotiate contracts; coordinate with lenders, builders, inspectors and title companies to come to a smooth, on time close.

REAL ESTATE BROKER: PRUDENTIAL HIGH DESERT REALTY, BEND, OR 2011-2012

Full time Real Estate Buyer's Specialist on Team Birtola Garmyn. Contacted leads in the Boomtown database management system to gain clients, showed homes, negotiated contracts, coordinated with lenders, inspectors and title companies to come to a smooth, on time close.

ASSISTANT, MANAGER: INDEPENDENT CONTRACTOR, OR 2009-Current

Business oversight, marketing, sales, wedding coordinator, and photographer for established businesses.

EXECUTIVE ASSISTANT: EDGENET, INC., ATLANTA, GA 2008-2009

Administrative support for the President and CEO, CFO, and Sr. Vice President including production of reports, presentations and correspondence; managed and coordinated all office staff requirements for travel itineraries and BOD meetings; maintained calendars and supplies.

EXECUTIVE ASSISTANT: SCHERER INDUSTRIAL PRODUCTS, ATLANTA, GA

Supported the President/Owner by creating all correspondence and reports; coordinated sampling, quotes, purchasing and shipping with multiple principals; maintained calendar, arranged extensive travel itineraries and set appointments; managed the office essentials.

LEGAL SECRETARY: BOVIS, KYLE & BURCH, ATLANTA, GA

Assisted five attorneys in preparing pleadings and motions for filing in the firm's cases, entered billing and printed client invoices, created and handled client files. Researched previously written documentation to create appropriate complaints and answers.

REAL ESTATE SALESPERSON: KELLER WILLIAMS REALTY, ATLANTA, GA 2000-2007

Represented buyers and sellers in new and resale residential sales through advertising and coordinating a team of professionals, including attorneys, title agents, builders, inspectors, appraisers and loan officers, to timely close on the sale of homes through completion of contracts.

OFFICE MANAGER: FIRE SYSTEMS SPECIALISTS, ATLANTA, GA 1993-2000

Computerized and automated invoicing, customer data, and bookkeeping. Responsible for all correspondence and communication with corporate accounts, accounts payables and receivables.

EDUCATION

AMBASSADOR UNIVERSITY, TX - ASSOCIATE OF ARTS 1983

DEVRY INSTITUTE, GA - BUSINESS STUDIES 2008

SKILLS

High proficiency in producing correspondence, presentations, reports and maintaining customer or product database and web sites utilizing **Microsoft Office Suite**, **Dictaphone**, **FrontPage** and contact management database systems. Also proficient using **Mac** applications such as **Pages**, **Numbers** and **Mail**.

Track expenses and financials utilizing **QuickBooks**, **Quicken**, **Excel** or other accounting or spreadsheet software.

Arrange travel itineraries, coordinate calendars, events, meetings and conferences utilizing **Internet Explorer** and **Microsoft Outlook**.

PROFESSIONAL REFERENCES

Bob Scherer Scherer Industrial Products, Inc. President/Owner (404) 252-8877 ras@sipinc.com

Charles Medlin
Bovis, Kyle & Burch
Partner
(678) 457-7607
cmm@boviskyle.com

Tom Clement
Edgenet, Inc.
Sr. Vice President
(404) 226-4223
tclement@edgenet.com